1548040858|**|<h3>Exercise</h3><h3>The Resistance</h3><p>We have stepped, pedaled and rolled for fitness, but are we ready to hang?</p><p>Full story: <a href='https://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/23/style/spiderbands-resistance-fitness.html'>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/23/style/spiderbands-resistance-fitness.html</a></p><h3>Health and Fitness:Weight Loss Articles from EzineArticles.com</h3><h3>Weight Training Versus Cardio for Losing Weight</h3><p>Lifting heavy weights raises the metabolic rate after the training ends. It works equally for men and women. The calorie burn can last up to 38 hours after the workout. Training with weights enables you to hold onto and tone the muscle. The body burns body fat to release the energy to repair and rebuild muscle. So you build muscle and lose fat at the same time. A win win situation.</p><p>Full story: <a href='http://EzineArticles.com/9895006'>http://EzineArticles.com/9895006</a></p><h3>Reasons Why You May Need Efficient Weight Loss Today And Not Putting It Off Any Longer</h3><p>When it comes to losing weight, lots of females are able to come up with an unlimited number of reasons as to why they can't shed weight or reasons as to why this crucial issue must be pushed off to the side for now. Weight loss, even a little, can significantly enhance your self-confidence and the way that you see yourself in addition to the way you think that others see you. If you dislike looking at yourself in the mirror every morning, it might be time to think about getting serious and begin a plan.</p><p>Full story: <a href='http://EzineArticles.com/9947398'>http://EzineArticles.com/9947398</a></p><h3>Weight Loss Versus Weight Gain</h3><p>In the last few weeks my sudden heart attack sent me into the cardiology ward of the local hospital. Although thinking my body was generally healthy and because I do not take in sugar or salt I was somewhat amazed at the food served in the ward. Much of what I had excluded from my diet was presented to me on the tray for lunch and dinner over the course of the first day.</p><p>Full story: <a href='http://EzineArticles.com/9947212'>http://EzineArticles.com/9947212</a></p><h3>10 Useful Running Tips for Effective Weight Loss</h3><p>Running is a great exercise for the mind and body. It is a great way to improve fitness and give your mood a boost. As simple as running can be, as beneficial it is to the body and mind, especially for weight loss, there is a correct way of doing it (that means there are also wrong ways of doing it, wow). The purpose of this article however is to help you understand some important thing you need to know and do for you to do it right.</p><p>Full story: <a href='http://EzineArticles.com/9927085'>http://EzineArticles.com/9927085</a></p><h3>Health and Fitness:Weight Loss Articles from EzineArticles.com</h3><h3>Weight Loss: Developing Your Personal Fat Loss Program</h3><p>Do you want shedding pounds? When you are, you might have been informed to construct your personal weight loss plan. Diet plans, which actually function as handbooks and inspiration for several some individuals, have already been recognized by help many achieve fat reduction aims.</p><p>Full story: <a href='http://EzineArticles.com/10040807'>http://EzineArticles.com/10040807</a></p>